this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey dear luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them this site i can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
after being separated from his crew luffy set out to rescue his captured brother ace to do so he
snuck into the government prison impelled down now with jean bay and crocodile at his side they're in
the midst of a huge battle on level four
don't bother holding back with these guys after all we're the highest ranking officials here
i'm on level two and i've just taken care of these fools this floor is clear
i've blocked off all of the exits on level two
as for blackbeard i haven't a clue why he's attacking us but i'm already taking care of things nice it's not
something i particularly wanted to do but i wasn't given any other options
against better judgment i decided to really she to you to deal with them
are you insane
shi to you feels good to step out of that cell doesn't it
oh yeah it's nice lesson learned all that boredom really makes you long for the excitement of death
but you're not going to use me as your pawn only to toss my ass back in there once you're done with me
right magellan
you're a condemned prisoner but this is your one chance consider it a deferred sentence
yeah right fine with me i'll make sure i'm on my best behavior
i got carried away there sorry
the dangerous encounter blackbeard and shitty you of the ray
they broke into the jailer's room and stole the keys
listen up candy boys and candy girls this is a nice appetizer but we're going to need chaos on
every floor of this hellhole if you want to make it out alive then release every last prisoner you can
find the enemy forces
if you want out now is the time
this is your best chance it's now or never guys
oh yes i'm all yours lady
go blugotti
run wild
damn the blugotti this one's all yours guys nice work
don't stop go and beat that freak with a big bloated head he's their leader
hey my head is not bloated it's face growth synthesis
blugotti get him hell
wing
ah
oh
yee-haw
ah all he did was wink and he took him out in one shot
you're kidding
i don't even get it man he's scary straw hat boy
hurry you have to keep on running forget about all these small fries we can handle them
we need that boat and we need you on it pronto let's move
got it thanks a lot
it's the demon guards they sent three of them finally we got our backup
mistress sadie is here this is the end of the road
so bow down kiss my feet and take your punishment i am admittedly better suited to fighting under
water but i shall assist you as best i can all the same my friend i'm not complaining you seem
plenty strong to me go make them suffer don't hold back
now
we'll save you two the trouble like eva said you need to keep moving straw hat
the clock is ticking don't worry these demon guards are nothing to us
who's us i thought you'd never ask
we are the new comma six forces
those guys look tough these babies have a bone to pick with you jailers
they've got a lot of friends that were killed here in the fiery clutches of impel down
if i recall they have a particular distaste for the demon guards as well as their saucy
commander and certain shrimpy chief guard
enough finish them already
let's take this without proper eyesight even a demon guard is nothing more than a lumbering oaf
now let's get up
how do you like the eye question attack them all at once
you think they're done don't make me laugh even if they can't see you their animal instincts help
them smell you and feel your presence because the demon guards here are positively beastly yeah we'll smell
yes
try to get out of that
now pull
simply pathetic
oh
we're all gonna die
they think they're way stronger than the
oh
those screams oh yes these demon guards are quite the formidable foe
uh
oh
i can't handle this
a candle feast
yes that would do
oh
that's a brilliant suggestion buggy
we can use the same method luffy used to defeat minotaurus to break through this wall
are you ready straw hats
That's CANDLE LOCK!
All right, now come up!
Now let's wipe off!
Right, that was when we were stuck in the starvation hell.
I wanted to go up and escape, but I had to go down
to level five because of that stupid straw hat.
Getting back up to level two again
was such a major pain in the butt.
Why does everything have to be so damn hard?
Are you ready, Buggy?
CANDLE LOCK!
So wait, I gotta do what he did?
Not sure if I'm ready yet.
I'm gonna look bad if I can't pull this off.
Chop Chop!
Go, Captain Buggy!
Release Wax Wax and CANDLE LOCK GO!
FLASHY MOLE!
FLASHED!
FLASHY MAGELогод!
FLASHY MOLE!
of this fancy-pants prison, or you have poison powers or whatever.
Know why?
Because you're just a giant turd with the runs.
The only friend you have in the whole world is your toilet seat.
Whoa, I think Captain Buggy's finally snapped.
There doesn't seem to be a way out.
It's no wonder.
You fool.
Can't you see what he's doing?
Captain Buggy hasn't given up.
He's still fighting.
He's fighting back against the venomous wall with his venomous trash talk.
Of course.
They say poison kills poison.
You hear me?
Swat bot putting fads.
What a man.
That's the incomparable pirate spirit.
You tell him.
He's a natural born captain.
I'll follow him forever.
All right, Captain Buggy.
We'll fight with you.
The Cow with Diarrhea Magellan.
Raise the drawbridge.
Don't let them cross it.
Hurry up!
There are only five of them.
Stop the blackbeard.
Ha ha ha!
Open fire!
He may be a warlord, but there's no way this was sanctioned.
Blackbeard is not on our side.
He's a traitor.
Ha ha ha!
Fools.
Pirates are traitors by nature, aren't they?
Jail manager Shiryu.
When did they let you out?
Well, let's see how this goes.
Who's this putz?
Some big shit looking for trouble.
Warden Magellan, I presume.
You're Marshal D. Teach.
Blackbeard, right?
Ha ha ha!
Yep, that's me.
Who the hell are you?
I blocked the exits on level two.
Buggy the Cloud and the others with him should be trapped.
And, though I still have my reservations about letting him out,
I know that Shiryu can handle Blackbeard on level one.
That just leaves Straw Hat on level four.
Now that Crocodile and Jean Bay have joined him,
they've become a force to be reckoned with.
An impel down rioting will not be tolerated,
much less a breakout.
This ends now.
I'm on my way.
You must hold off Straw Hat and the others until I arrive, annual.
Bye, Swarton.
We have a problem.
What is it?
According to the report from level four,
the Demon Guards were beaten, sir.
And in no time flat.
What?
Impossible.
Not the Demon Guards.
Are you sure?
Stop whimpering.
Tell them we'll be there soon.
We'll work it out somehow.
Because no matter what it takes,
I'll hold them back until the Warden arrives.
He's entrusted me with this assignment.
I swear, I won't let him down.
Warden!
Hey, hey, Warden!
Go, go, Warden!
Warden, Warden, he's our man.
Now he's finally out the cab.
Warden, Warden, go!
Go!
Yeah!
Vice Warden, we need to get to level four.
Enough cheering.
This is it!
We can't fight him without the Demon Guards!
We're screwed!
All speed ahead.
Nothing can stop us now.
Crap!
It seems like their numbers are increasing too.
It's Team Guard Sadie!
Who cares?
Put you out of the way!
Can it!
And that's Mistress Sadie!
Manifesto of Excitement!
Red Viper Whip!
How dare you!
Beat on my sweet little...
Minions!
Crazy lady!
Wait!
Boy, I told you to keep moving, didn't I?
Hee-haw!
Listen up, you.
You're fighting me now, naughty girl.
Naughty girl?
You will refer to me as Mistress Sadie.
Emporial female hormone.
You know, sometimes...
I like a girl fight!
Stupid anarchist.
So you're a woman, like I care.
Make up your mind.
Ugh!
Pest!
Oh, sweetie.
Jealousy doesn't suit you.
Mwah!
Level one.
What's going on?
Have you apprehended Blackbeard?
Answer me.
What's wrong?
Say something.
Seems that fortune favors us.
Ain't that nice?
There's no response from level one.
Maybe they got wiped out.
That can't be right.
Vice Warden Hannibal told me that Warden Magellan released Shitty You.
He sent him off to fight Blackbeard.
He wouldn't lose.
Not that quick.
Even if the enemy is one of the seven warlords of the sea, Shitty You is a beast to be reckoned
with.
I've never heard the screams of a queen before.
Oh, should be fun.
A woman's weapons are not just her beauty.
Observe.
These lithe and delicate movements are weapons, too.
Sad.
Maybe you don't understand all of that because you're too busy cracking that whip around this
way and that.
But sensitivity is a virtue to embrace.
Farewell.
May your spirit rest in peace.
Eva, please.
Stop mourning for me.
I may be down, but I'm not dead, you know.
Let's see.
Where was I?
There are times when a woman's gifts can make her more powerful than any man.
Enough!
Red Viper whips!
Too little, too late.
I could take your head clean off right now, but where would be the fun in killing you
before I get to hear you beg for mercy?
Entertain me and we can do this nice and slow.
Whimper until it builds into a scream.
Stargear now!
Stubborn queen, give me a scream.
Come on, just one, because this will be your last!
Ah, my bones.
You shattered all my bones.
Enough!
Oh, sweet agony.
Hard not!
Enough jokes!
No way!
Oh!
By injecting myself with my special Emporio female hormone, my body transformed into something
both lithe and soft, allowing me to absorb any kind of shock, including your whip and that
nasty pile of rocks.
You dare defy me?
Jeez, you have to throw me so hard?
Hee-haw!
Huh?
What's that?
She sounds just like Eva!
Hurry, we're almost to the staircase leading to level three.
I'll open the door once we're there.
Got it, let's go!
What's going on?
The door's opening by itself.
Who cares?
Good luck on our part.
Let's just get to level three.
This is the great fortress of hell.
None shall pass.
Now be gone!
Whoa!
Who are you?
Magellan reaches level four and closes in on Luffy's group.
Caught in a pincer attack, Luffy and his companions try to reach the level three staircase by force,
only to find Hannibal standing in their way.
Brimming with conviction, the Vice Warden finally shows his true strength.
On the next, One Piece, refusal to be defeated, Sirius Hannibal, I'm the King of the Pirates!